Heavy fog before dawn.
Dead calm again today.
Woke up at the same time as usual.
Spent an hour getting ready.
AM.
Went out with the Entourage to ascertain our situation.
Visually confirmed that there is nothing of note anywhere.
Inventoried remaining supplies.
We need a way out of here.
Miss Re-l...
Vincent.
Vincent!
What?
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
Two thousand miles to Mosk.
But here, the lull has been... never-ending.
Despite everything, PROXIES...
Their mystery remains unsolved.
Not only unsolved, it deepens... Nothing makes sense anymore.
To what extent are we being deceived?
And the greatest mystery of all
is the one right in front of me.
meditation   dead calm
Good morning.
Observed PROXY behavior all day.
Lameness.
Is leaving the toilet seat up the
only way you can show your manliness?
Vincent!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Weren't you listening when I told you to put the seat back down?!
I was-
No, you weren't!
Due to boredom, attempted observation of infected autoreiv.
I see.
Journeys are often likened to one's life.
A pinch of salt?
What a vague instruction.
A new discovery in this unknown...
At times, I am surprised...
Dammit!
No way!
What is this?!
Lunch meal preparation.
Examined new facet of the cogito virus.
Are you left-handed as well?
Left-handed?
Autoreivs are designed to be ambidextrous.
Is being left-handed despite that a psychosomatic effect?
Is it good, Lady?
It's hard.
Any conclusion regarding the
autoreiv's arm dexterity will have to wait.
Now that I think about it,
I know nothing about PROXIES
nor about Vincent Law.
What?
Oh, don't mind me.
Found it.
You have a hole.
Oh, don't mind it.
Whether there's a need to know...
That is the question.
PM.
The feared supply shortage issue surfaced suddenly.
3, 2, 1.
Miss Re-l, it's been three minutes.
I haven't washed my hair yet.
But if you consider the remaining water supply...
I want to wash my hair today, no matter what!
Miss Re-l!
Two more minutes!
You have short hair, so you only need one minute, right?
But that's...
Temporary solution to the water
supply issue achieved after negotiations.
What's wrong?
I'm training my eyeballs.
AM.
Significant decrease in morale among crew members.
It's been three hours already.
What in the world are they doing?
The food shortage is only getting worse.
Are you thinking, "Not beans again"?
Well, yes...
but the way you arranged them...
I thought it might be a good idea to make it look different.
I am extremely skeptical of such behavior,
not to mention, just looking at his
placid face somehow irritates me.
PM.
No change.
New socks...
How idiotic.
What's this?
When traveling under such circumstances,
there are moments when certain insurmountable barriers
become tangible truths - barriers between humans and PROXIES,
between man and cogito-infected autoreiv,
that prevent them from achieving true coexistence
and separate their existences from one another.
Incomprehensible.
Huh?
Look, look!
Not again... She'll get mad at you.
I'll draw on your face too, Vince.
Stop that!
Look, look!
Stop that...
But if you're going to do it anyway,
how about a little more...
Oh, it's Re-l.
Look, look at Vince!
You look like you're enjoying yourself.
Um...
I'm sorry!
Miss Re-l!
I suddenly realize that,
faced with an endless horizon,
we are unbelievably fragile and powerless.
What do you think about this situation?
Have you thought of a solution?
A "solution", you say...
but if there is no wind, we can't do anything, so...
"So"?
So, well...
"Well" what?
No, it's nothing.
What do you mean, "It's nothing"?
You've come up with nothing after thinking long and hard?
Or is it that you haven't even tried?
Who gave you the authority to put dressing on shared food items?
Why do I have to go along with your preferences?
Um, well...
If you have something to say, say it loud and clear.
I don't feel you have any initiative.
Same goes for this journey.
It's all by the seat of your pants!
Do you have any sense of purpose?
Th-That'll become clear once I reach Mosk...
I'm sure...
I'm sorry.
Self-deprecation isn't the answer.
I'm sorr...
Why are you so wishy-washy?
Stop making that "what's this woman bitching about?" face.
You're ruining my appetite!
Well, um...
Personally, I think the wind will eventually
start back up again if we just sit back and wait...
Why did you just change subjects?
Right now, we're talking about your...
Forget it.
Still bored.
Observed autoreiv to pass the time.
No way!
What's this?!
Stop making that "what's this woman bitching about?" face.
You're ruining my appetite!
Chronic lassitude,
decline in ability to think...
I can only see problems.
Miss Re-l?
At times, I've tried to understand.
But, it was futile.
Snow fell before dawn.
Navigation distance remains unchanged.
Woke up at the same time as usual.
Confirmed situation.
Lull persists.
On days that chill you to the bone, your mind wakes up,
but your body resists.
God, it's freezing!
It's snow!
Re-l!
Snow! It's snow!
Let's go play together!
Re-l!
C'mon.
C'moooon...
Pino!
Look, it's the aurora!
What's that?
Wow! So pretty!
Stupid!
Stupid wind!
...wind!
Come get me!
...me!
What is he doing?
I'm your foe!
...your foe!
I don't get it.
Dammit! Damn you!
Damn you, you bastard!
There!
Damn you!
Drastically limiting use of electricity for the foreseeable future.
She's totally staring at me.
She's saying something too.
I wonder what she's saying.
There...
Could Miss Re-l be...
No way.
I feel cornered - possibly a sign of malnutrition.
The tension only increases.
Am I at my limit?
Slept deeply for the first time in a while.
Dreamt of Iggy.
Can only rely on my spirit.
Vincent, the candle.
Oh, okay.
OW!
What was that for?
Never mind.
What?
Don't make a funny face.
Oww...
Jeez, you're such a...
Are you all right?
Yay!
Pino! Wait!
Stupid wind!
...wind!
Come get me!
...me!
Miss Re-l...
I'm your foe!
...your foe!
It really clears your head, doesn't it.
Vince, you just went "thud"!
Don't laugh!
Come get me!
Maybe the solution is unexpectedly simple.
Take that!
You got me!
Thinking about it is useless.
I decided to adopt that mindset.
Besides, for some reason, right now I feel...
Pino!
...a bit as though I can let myself smile.
Wind!
Two thousand miles to Mosk.
Brisk winds from the southwest.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Insanity wanders in an abandoned paradise.
A shadow writhes in the abandoned ruins.
Their emotions now unleash lightning.
meditation  endless battle